(Sheldon:)It should take you
no more than three hours.
Well, wait, how many questions
are on this thing?
(Sheldon:)Only 211.
Don't worry. I've kept them all
at a high-school graduate reading level.
(Penny:)Thanks, pal.
(Sheldon:)You got it, buddy.
(Penny:)Sheldon, honey, did you ever consider
making friends by being...
(Penny:)...I don't know, pleasant?
(Sheldon:)Well, that's certainly
a thought-provoking hypothesis.
(Sheldon:)May I suggest it
as the topic for your essay?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Your questionnaire, very disappointing.
(Leonard:)I answered every question, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You answered the multiple choice
questions in a pattern.
A-B-B-A-C, A-B-B-A-C.
- Oh, you picked up on that, huh?
- Yeah, wait...
(Sheldon:)How could I not?